Here we go!
This time I'll be talking with Rika Sasaki of Angulum
Hisaki Emoto of Juice Chus!
This show is about the behind-the-scenes production of the various artists
We're going to take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
Our recording, rehearsals, etc.
We will show you the process of our recording and rehearsal.
Let's start with the two of us.
I, Sasaki, had a release event for our new song released on December 13th.
We had a release event.
We went back to the original format of the release event.
The way we put the audience in and the closeness of the event, the volume of the voice, and the feeling of the audience.
I think it makes the audience feel differently.
I think there are a lot of differences in the way the audience feels about it.
I could feel the joy of returning to the original form with my whole body.
Thanks to all of you, we were able to have a very enjoyable event this time, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I'm so glad that there was no acrylic board, because sometimes you can't hear the music at all when it's there.
I'm so happy that I didn't have that... I'm so happy too.
As for me, Evata, JuiceJuice's performance at Nippon Budokan has ended successfully!
Thank you for your hard work!
For this Nippon Budokan concert, they performed a medley that they didn't perform in the fall tour.
The medley was
There were a lot of mistakes during the rehearsal, so I made a lot of mistakes.
There was a part in the middle of the "I love you" romance where we had to jump, but it was suddenly very short and we missed the jump.
It was like, "Oh, I'm sorry, I forgot...
I'm so relieved now that the show ended without a hitch, but I think it must have been really hard for the fans to hear the chorus for the first time, because we were struggling like that at first.
I'm sure it was a lot of work, but I'm so glad that the fans were able to follow us.
I'm really proud of you.
Did you wear any of your old costumes?
Yes, they were.
It was really interesting.
I don't know.
I think it's really nice to have moments that remind us of the past, so I think it was a wonderful live performance.
I hope we can continue to do our best in the future.
Now, let's start from here!
The making of Angulum Red Line music video shooting
The latest single of Angeleum, Red Line, was released on December 13th.
Here's a sneak peek at the making of the music video for Red Line, the latest single from Angulum, released on December 13th!
Se-no, up-cam is about to start!
It's going around!
Okay, here we go. Here we go. Music, please.
Yes, up-camiiiiiiiiiii!
The shooting of the music video for Red Line has begun.
Let's see,
First of all, we are filming the lip scene,
This time, it's the Red Line,
And then there were red sneakers in the background,
Also, the dance shot was very unique to the red line,
The background of the dance shot is also very unique to the Red Line,
I would like you to pay attention to that as well.
Also, the new members, Shimoitori, Yukiho and Hana Goto, are in their first music video,
This is their first music video,
I am looking forward to seeing their new expressions.
I'll do my best!
I'm Hana Goto.
I'm Shimoi, and this is Yukiho.
Well, let's see, we just joined Koanzurumu,
This is our first music video shoot,
What time is it now?
It is the time when we are observing the seniors, the seniors doing their thing.
Yes, that's what it's about, so we are now watching the seniors and seeing how cool they are,
We are learning a lot from them, and now we are going to start the show,
I hope to do my best.
Good luck!
Please use that to your advantage and move in various ways.
Red Line
Hurt.
I want to hurt you.
I do, I do, I'm your favor
I want to spill it.
Red Line
This scar
Proof that I'm ready
I'm hot, I'm hot, I'm hot
I'll show it to you.
Red Line
It was very difficult.
After all, when I watched the video, I thought, "Oh, I'll do this, or I'll do that,
But when I stood in front of the camera, I was so conscious of my part,
But when I stood there, I was so conscious of my part that I forgot what to do,
I would forget or wonder what I should do,
I forget, I wonder what I should do, and I do the same things over and over again,
I do the same things all the time, and I think, "Oh, this is the kind of pattern that I need to gain experience in,
I think, "Oh, this is the kind of pattern I need to gain experience," and that's what I look forward to.
I also look forward to working with Mr. Sasagi and Mr. Kawamura,
Basically, the way they are sitting now is really cool, but sometimes I want them to look at me a little,
But sometimes I want them to look at me,
It's not so much that I want them to look at me, but rather that I want them to look at me,
It's more like an image shot, so I'd like to see a glimpse of the camera, or something like that,
I want you to look at the camera a little bit, or look away from the camera, or something like that.
Come on, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. 41
refuse
credits
dea
please
me
Unconsciousness, without charge
warmed up, hidden in my eyes
Today's voice
Now, now, now sex
Pray blue explosiveness
Transcend
Let the light continue
Hurt the day
I do I do I will stay on
I want to go beyond Love Feeds Death
Let the light
A symbol of determination
I could dream
I'll charm you
Send a light
The show is called the Red Line.
Leila line?
It's not a line, but it's so beautiful.
Yes, you did a great job with the dancing this time, didn't you?
We worked really hard. We split it in half.
We all gave advice to each other, regardless of seniority or juniority.
We worked really hard, so today's dance shot was done with a lot of energy!
reportedly
show
by H.
Yes, I went around!
Thank you very much.
The music video shoot is over. It's for Red Line. It was the first music video shoot since the new organization was formed.
It was the first music video shoot since the new formation of Angstrom, and the atmosphere in the free time became brighter with the addition of Yukiho and Hana Goto on the lower board.
The music video is very cool, and the song is also very cool.
As the title "Red Line" suggests, the song is about a girl who wants to cross a line that she shouldn't cross but can't. The lyrics and the choreography are all about the frustration of not being able to cross that line.
The choreography is also pretty cool, and the dancers really dance their hearts out.
I dance with a lot of gusto.
I hope you will pay attention to that. I hope you will pay attention to that as well. I think it's a really great music video, so please watch it as much as you can. Please watch it a lot.
Yes, Red Line is a new song that has come down to us,
So the atmosphere was different from the past, but my impression was that everyone was doing different things,
I love the cool dance that you can feel the power of all the dancers when they are all together.
That's what I want you to pay attention to.
I'm sure you saw the music video earlier.
You may have seen in the music video earlier, everyone is sitting on chairs and doing it.
It was summer when we were filming.
It was summer.
It was really hot in the studio.
Oh, no. Would I get swallowed?
It was really hot.
But you didn't show that kind of expression, and you looked cool.
I had my nails done for the day of the music video.
I thought it was important to have my hands on my lips for the lip scene and so on.
I thought it was important, so I did it to motivate myself.
But when it came time for the dance shot, I did my nails...
What?
I thought it was painful, but then my nails fell off.
I thought it was painful, but then I found a nail rolled off. Gel?
There's a sculpting technique.
It's such an intense dance.
When I enter the floor, there's a part where I go into the floor and then I go up.
I think I was straining too hard and the nail came off.
This is a very behind-the-scenes story, but I don't think I've ever told it before.
What did you do with the nail?
The nails, I mean. They fell out of his pockets.
Are there any more nails at the end?
You remember the scene with the Green Mac? I didn't have any nails.
I didn't think so.
I don't think she'll know because she's not in the picture. But between you and me...
It's all between you and me.
But despite that, it's a really great music video.
I hope you all enjoy it.
Me too!
The rap-like part before the chorus of this song.
with Kokoerin-chan.
and the part where the song modulates at the end.
I'm so happy!
So you'll actually see me at the Budokan?
Yes, I saw it.
It was really cool. We were so excited.
Thank you very much.
That's all for the making of the Angstrom Red Line music video shoot.
Thank you for your hard work!
Next, here we go.
Morning Musume。23 すごいフィーバー Dance Lesson
Here is the dance lesson of "Sukkoukou Fever" from Morning Musume。23's latest single.
Door ball, I'm sorry for a minute now. I was thinking of adding four more. The two in the back are already standing, yes. And the rest of you, please go outside so that I can't see your faces anymore.
Yes, sideways. Then, in order from the back, 5&6&7&.
Yes. Listen to the clicks, and then click, click, click, click, 5&6&7&.
And let's go. Yes. 5&6&7&.
Yes. 5&6&7&.
Yes. 5&6&&. Yes. yes. yes.
Yes, yes. You all walked into the position, and you pointed your fingers, oh, don't sit on this right away. Yes, yes. First of all, he pointed his finger, he pointed his finger, Rikuta turns and sits with him.
Hmmm. I wonder when, I'm sorry.
Yes. Yes, I'm sorry.
But it's not the story you want.
No. Uh, sorry about the bartender.
Have you finished your etfi banner?
opposing Даn TAN.
In such a case, um, if you hear it from the outside, you should put your face in the box too.
She런 feeling.
Right?
Hey, you know what?
na,
Hey, hey, hey,
From the outside, yeah. So, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
Thank you for watching.
P-p-p-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa.
P-p-p-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa!
Pass!
That's great! That's great!
Here we are, one lifetime at a time. Change the times!
Oh, my gosh! That's great!
Once a lie, it won't be long before it's over!
I'm embracing all that youth has to offer.
You know what?
More than any family I've ever spent time with.
I get to be the best of friends with the birds.
Reverse. Fun, fun, fun. Hey, hey, hey.
I'm not going anywhere.
Reverse funfun, hey!
You should switch to that.
Looks like you made your choice.
I'm sure we'll all be happy.
Ah...
We've been like
From the front
Bubba Bubba
Dance lesson has finished. Thank you very much.
How was it? How are the members this time?
Who are the members this time? Yes, it was good.
I was the first one to choreograph with the 17th term, so I was a bit worried about that,
Yes, I was. But the songs are also very friendly,
Yes, yes.
I think the atmosphere was good.
It was good.
There are three singles this time, and this was the third song out of three that we had to choreograph.
So when we finished one song at a time and were talking about what was going to happen,
I will never forget the shock I felt when the dummy instructor showed me the song,
I really enjoyed it.
I thought, "I knew it was Yoshiko,
I was really impressed,
I was really moved, and I was so happy that Yoshiko-sensei, who had helped me so much, could choreograph my last single,
I was so happy to be able to choreograph the last single,
I'm really happy that Ms. Yoshiko, who has helped me a lot, was able to choreograph the last single for me,
I also feel that it is a wonderful song that I can really get excited with my fans.
The theme of the song was requested to be something that everyone can dance to together,
I thought it would be great if I could do the chorus and introduction with the audience,
So I stepped into it,
I was dancing with the fans,
This time, I was allowed to use dummies,
I had the dummies come to the show for the first time in three years,
The dummies then copied the dances for the members,
The dummies were so excited that they started oohing and ahhing,
They were so excited that they started woofing and woofing.
That surprised me.
I knew I was really moved.
I was really moved by the way they made the scene with my classmates,
There are a lot of parts like that.
I was amazed at the formation of the teacher.
I mean, the "dururur" part of the A melody,
There is no way that the three people at the back would sing the part where the A melody goes "dururuuru".
There is no such thing.
Yes, so I really enjoy that kind of formation change,
So, you can enjoy it with your eyes as well,
So it is a wonderful song that can be enjoyed with the eyes and also with the calls.
That's why I am a little bit aware that I am not good at the dance of one of the dancers,
I'm aware that I'm not very good at it,
Is that so?
I'm aware that I'm not very good at it yet,
I hope I can make it better by the day of the music video.
Thank you for your cooperation.
I'm looking forward to the performance.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to seeing Morning Musume's formation dance and so on,
I was really impressed by Morning Musume's formation dance and the power of their canon,
I wonder what it is about the choreography,
I felt that I could dance with them at the next live performance,
So I'm really looking forward to it. I'm already looking forward to it.
Yes, I thought the choreography was really catchy, fun, and cute,
I was also impressed by the music video with everyone wearing pink jackets,
I was also impressed by the way everyone was wearing pink jackets in the music video, and the way the jackets were fluttered around was very typical of Yoshiko,
I thought it was very Morning Musume-like,
I thought it was very Morning Musume-like, and the two of them, Getter-chan and Haru-san, Shimeba,
I could feel that Getter-chan, Haru-san, and Shimeba-san were really getting on everyone's nerves in this dance lesson,
It was really cute.
I thought it was really cute,
I thought it was really cute, and the way they were working so hard, doing their best, it was really sparkling,
I'm really looking forward to seeing them in the future.
That's all for now, Morning Musume。 23's dance lesson was a blast.
Are you having fun? Please watch the rest of the show.
Thank you for watching.
Rika Sasaki of Angelem
Juice Juice's Kisaki Ebata is here with up-cam.
Here's the next one!
Juice Juice Wonderful World 2023 Juice Juice Ver. Vocal Recording
From Juice Juice's latest album
Wonderful World 2023 Juice Juice Ver. Vocal Recording by Riai Matsunaga!
Well, first of all, let's take a quick shot of my part.
Dotamar's part of the A melody, right?
Yes, sir.
Okay, let's start from there.
Okay.
Dotamar's part of the A melody
If I hadn't met you...
Because I met you...
Let's laugh like crazy.
Yes!
Because I met you.
OK.
Okay.
Let's go to the chorus.
I'm going to skip to the chorus.
Okay.
Take your part.
Yes, sir.
Because I met you...
It's a wonderful world, isn't it?
What a great love I'm surrounded by.
When you're here, when I think of you
That's all it takes to make this place a wonderforver
Okay.
Yes, ma'am.
It's a beautiful day
You say love me
And I say love you
Only you
OK, let's go to LaLaLa
Yes, please.
Then we'll go straight to the two of you.
Yes, sir.
Only you forever
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
Yes, yes, yes, yes, that's what I mean.
Only the last one
Yes
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
Yes.
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la.
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
諩 follow
lalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalala
Two things
It's time to think heads!
Oh, is it now?
Here's the line Mr. Matsunaga sings
Amazing!
It's hard to sing a line like this.
I don't remember this one.
It's so hard!
It's difficult.
It's pretty low.
Yes, sir.
It's not that high.
You can do it.
Let's do it.
Please do it.
It's a wonderful world, isn't it? What great love we have here.
Yes, yes, yes, that's what the line is about. I hope that comes out a little stronger. Yes, please.
This world is wonderful, isn't it?
What great love we are surrounded by.
Yes, OK.
Okay.
Now, let's continue.
Matsunaga-san, you are going to go to the all-you-can-eat place.
Yes, sir.
Basically, ha, ha, ha, ha, is fine.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I guess that's all.
Thank you very much.
What is the JuStory of this album?
Font Voyage, one new song called "Miracle of Thoughts" and 13 past songs,
and 13 songs from the past,
I re-recorded this album with the current members,
All the songs from the past were sung by me, but the junior members sang their own parts,
But the junior members will sing their own part of the songs, plus their own part,
The younger members sing their own song assignments plus the ones they would like to sing,
If they liked it, they had a chance to sing that part of the song,
Some members got more assignments there,
Some of the members got more song assignments there, but it was a style of recording that had not been used very often before,
We recorded 13 songs in a style that had not been used very often,
I remember that it was a lot of fun.
I remember how much fun it was to record 13 songs in that style,
I was very happy to hear her voice, which has a core, but I love it so much, and it makes me want to listen to it all the time, on the recording.
I was so happy to hear her voice on the recording,
When I listen to her voice live, it enters my body and stays with me forever.
Hmmm...
Yes, there was a feeling that stayed with me, and I was listening to her, thinking that she has a very attractive voice, and that she expresses herself in a very attractive way, but there was one thing I was wondering about.
Rabbit? There is a lyric card, and a rabbit-like thing appeared next to the lyric card, and I wondered what it was,
I wondered what it was, and when I told Yahana about it, she said it was her usual character,
The way she proceeded with the recording, it was like, "Yes, I understand.
She was like, "Yes, yes, I understand. I felt like, "Oh, that's Riai-chan," and her individual recording style comes out in each recording.
So, Riai-chan's recordings are very interesting, and there is something cool about the way she says "yes" and does it without hesitation,
It was really fun to watch, and I was reminded once again what a wonderful voice she has.
This is JuiceJuice Wonderful World 2023 JuiceJuice Ver. Riai Matsunaga's vocal recording.
Thank you for watching.
Morning Musume。23
Wake Up Call
When you wake up
Now on sale
It's going to be great!
This time, it's time to say goodbye to the up-cam of Kisaki Ebata, aka Rika Sasaki.
It's time to say goodbye. We've watched a lot of videos this time.
I, Ebata, have a great memory of the making of Angulum's Red Line music video.
Well, I mean, it's a memory, but it's a memory with me.
Memories.
I could feel how close you guys are just from the video.
I felt how close you guys are just from the video.
Ms. Sasaki, who was watching the video, was saying how cute the members looked every time they were on the screen.
It's embarrassing.
I felt his love for them.
Thank you very much for your love. I was really impressed by Juice Hariai-chan.
The recording was a real shock to me.
But there's a live performance of "3 of us" starting in the new year.
I'm going to be there with all the members of Sojuice.
I'd like to spend some time with Leah and Kisaki.
I'd like to cherish the time I can spend with everyone, including Leah and Kisaki.
I'd like to spend some time with Leah's rabbit.
I'm sure I'll be able to solve the mystery of the rabbit that Leah kept.
I hope to be able to solve the mystery of the rabbit that Leah kept.
I hope we can solve the mystery of Leah's rabbit.
We will be going behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
Please subscribe to our channel and we'll introduce you to the parts you don't normally see.
This time, we'll be talking with Rikako Sasaki of Angulum and
JuiceJuice's Hisaki Ebata.
Farewell!
Next time on Upokami, we'll be back with Risa Ogata, the making of the music video shoot for "Small World", and ,
Morning Musume。 23 WAKE UP CALL Waking Up recording.
Please look forward to it!
Thank you for watching.